const questions = [
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484ba3',
    answer: 'A'
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484ba4',
    answer: 'C',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484ba5',
    answer: 'D',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484ba6',
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484ba7',
    answer: 'C',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484ba8',
    answer: 'B',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484ba9',
    answer: 'D',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484ba0',
    answer: 'B',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484bb1',
    answer: 'C',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484bb2',
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484bb3',
    answer: 'B'
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484bb4',
    answer: 'C',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484bb5',
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484bb6',
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484bb7',
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484bb8',
    answer: 'C',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484bb9',
    answer: 'D',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484bc0',
    answer: 'D',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484bc1',
    answer: 'A',
  },
  {
    question: 'cc34fa8f751a4995b4dbfa4d1d484bbc2',
    answer: 'D',
  }
]

module.exports = questions;